

#### **PROFILE**

I began my professional technical work with Best Buy's Geek Squad. Since then, I have worked on projects that have taught me coding and communication skills, project management, marketing and ultimately helped me grow a love for technology and the internet.

As a member of the Eleven Fifty Academy alumni, it is my goal to use the skills I have acquired to build a successful career as a developer. Please contact me to discuss your company vision and values. Let me show you how I can be an asset to your team.

## **CONTACT**

PHONE: (765)717-1913

WEBSITE:

www.linkedin.com/in/chellemo

EMAIL:

Chellemo23@gmail.com

# MICHELLE SMITH

Android and Web Developer

## **EDUCATION**

## **Eleven Fifty Academy**

March 2019 – August 2019 Full Stack JavaScript Developer Certificate

### **Udemy**

August 2019 - Current Android Developer Certification (Completed: February 2020) Kotlin programming course (Currently enrolled)

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Real Otaku Gamer, Indie Games Contact Manager

January 2011-January 2012

Point of contact for indie game developers wanting to advertise their products on the Real Otaku Gamer website, writer, editor

## Pink and Deadly Co-founder, Co-producer

October 2009–October 2010

Co-founder and co-host of the Pink and Deadly video game podcast

## Best Buy, Counter Intelligence Agent

August 2006–March 2009

Bench technician, computer repair, customer service, sales

## **SKILLS**

JavaScript React.Js Node Java Kotlin

Android Studio

Visual Studio Code

IntelliJ Idea